<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Goonhammer - Kill Team</title><link>https://www.goonhammer.com/category/core-games/kill-team/</link><description>Kill Team posts</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 21:30:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Goonhammer Interviews the 2023 WCW Kill Team Top 8, Part 1: Players 5-8</title><link>https://www.goonhammer.com/goonhammer-interviews-2023-kill-team-world-championships-top-8-part-1/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://d1w82usnq70pt2.cloudfront.net/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/KillTeam_Banner.png"/&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year’s World Championship of Warhammer has come and gone, bringing with it reports that the Ork Kommando meta has fallen short of  the finish line. It seems Feel No Pains, Tentacles, and Mouths in odd places were the law of the land this year, with the top two slots having been dominated by Chaos Cultists teams. We covered the results of each group stage bracket last week, so this week it’s time to talk about the Top 8.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Goonhammer Interviews the Top 4 Players from the 2023 Kill Team World Championships</title><link>https://www.goonhammer.com/goonhammer-interviews-the-top-4-players-from-the-2023-kill-team-world-championships/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://d1w82usnq70pt2.cloudfront.net/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/KillTeam_Banner.png"/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to our nearly complete coverage the 2023 World Championships of Warhammer. Yesterday we took a look at the meta of the top 8 bracket at the event and spoke with the players who finished fifth through eighth. Today we’re looking at the championship bracket in full and talking to the top 4 players from the event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 18:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ringing at the Kill Team World Championships: An Event Report</title><link>https://www.goonhammer.com/ringing-at-the-kill-team-world-championships-an-event-report/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://d1w82usnq70pt2.cloudfront.net/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/KillTeam_Banner.png"/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Salutations readers, welcome to my recap of the 2023 World Championships of Warhammer, in which I played as a ringer!&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 14:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JAKTP Episode 42 – World Champions of Warhammer Live</title><link>https://www.goonhammer.com/jaktp-episode-42-world-champions-of-warhammer-live/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://d1w82usnq70pt2.cloudfront.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/29-128-265x198.png"/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join us in this episode as we follow along with Travis’s journey through the WCW. Goonhammer graciously allowed me to ring for the WCW (link here), and I spent some time interviewing players. We’ve got interviews with communities all around the world, including players from Poland, Mexico, and Australia. The other half of the interviews are on our Patreon!&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 20:02:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Final 2023 UTC Regular Season Standings</title><link>https://www.goonhammer.com/the-final-2023-utc-regular-season-standings/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://d1w82usnq70pt2.cloudfront.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/UTC_Banner1-534x462.png"/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first season of the Unified Tournament Circuit is closing out and it’s time to look at the final standings as we prep for the finale. The top 32 ranked players for Warhammer 40k and Age of Sigmar will receive invitations to the finals, each of which is a five-round GT to determine the circuit’s winners (also, there are some pretty sweet cash prizes in the mix). Players will be competing for $10,000 in total cash prizes in addition to other prizes supplied by Fabricator’s Forge.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 20:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>